I’m on the Next Level Yeah
절대적 룰을 지켜
絶対的なルールを守れ
I follow the absolute rules
내 손을 놓지 말아 결속은 나의 무기내 손을 놓지 말아 결속은 나의 무기
私の手を離さないで　結束は私の武器
Don't let go of my hand, unity is my weapon
광야로 걸어가
KWANGYAへ歩いていく
I walk to KWANGYA
알아 네 home ground
知っている　君のHome ground
I know your Home ground
위협에 맞서서 제껴라 제껴라 제껴라
威嚇に立ち向かって　追い抜け　追い抜け　追い抜け
Confront the threat, beat it, beat it, beat it
>woo-wee-woo wee aespa!
상상도 못한 Black out 유혹은 깊고 진해
想像もできなかったBlack out　誘惑は深くて濃い
An unexpected Black out, the temptation is deep and strong
맞잡은 손을 놓쳐 난 절대 포기 못해
取り合った手を離してしまう　私は絶対諦められない
Letting go of the hands held together, but I'll never give up
I’m on the Next Level
저 너머의 문을 열어
あの向こうのドアを開ける
I open the door over there
Next level 널
Next Level 君を
Next Level, I'll
결국엔 내가 부셔
ついには私が壊す
Destroy you in the end
Next Level KOSMO에 닿을 때까지
Next Level KOSMOに届くまで
Until I reach the Next Level KOSMO
>Next Level 제껴라 제껴라 제껴라
Next Level 追い抜け　追い抜け　追い抜け
Next Level, beat it, beat it, beat it
La la la la la la
La la la la la
I see the NU EVO
적대적인 고난과 슬픔은
敵対的な苦難と悲しみは
The hostile suffering and sorrow
널 더 popping 진화시켜
君をさらにPopping　進化させる
Make you Popping and evolve further
That’s my nævis It’s my nævis
You lead, we follow 감정들을 배운 다음
You lead, we follow　感情を学んだ後
You lead, we follow, after learning the feelings
Watch me while I make it out
Watch me while I work it out
Work it work it work it out
감당할 수 없는 절망도
耐えきれない絶望も
Even the unbearable despair
내 믿음을 깨지 못해
私の信頼を破ることはできない
Can't break my faith
더 아픈 시련을 맞아도 난
さらに苦しい試練に遭っても
Even if a more painful trial comes
잡은 손을 놓지 않을게 Oh
私は取った手を離さないから Oh
I won't let go of your hand Oh
Beat drop Naevis calling, ae!
절대로 뒤를 돌아보지 말아 (ae)
絶対に後ろを振り向かないで
Never look back
광야의 것 탐내지 말아 (ae)
KWANGYAのもの　欲しがるな
Don’t covet things of KWANGYA
약속이 깨지면 모두 걷잡을 수 없게 돼
約束が破れたら全て取り返しがつかなくなる
If the promises are broken, everything will be out of control
언제부턴가 불안해져 가는 신호
いつからか不安になっていく合図
The signal is becoming unstable since a certain point in time
널 파괴하고 말 거야 (We want it)
君を破壊してしまう
I'll destroy you in the end
Come on! Show me the way to KOSMO Yeah
Black Mamba가 만들어낸 환각 quest
Black Mambaが作り出した幻覚クエスト
A hallucination quest created by the Black Mamba
aespa, ae를 분리시켜놓길 원해 그래
aespa, aeを分離しておいてほしい　そう
aespa, They want to separate out ae, that’s right
중심을 잃고 목소리도 잃고
重心を失い　声も失い
I lose my balance and my voice too
비난받고 사람들과 멀어지는 착각 속에
非難されて　人たちと遠のく錯覚の中で
In the illusion of being criticized and alienated
nævis 우리 ae, ae들을 불러봐
nævis  私たち (ae, aeを呼んでみて)
nævis We (Call ae, ae)
aespa의 Next Level "P.O.S"를 열어봐
aespaの Next Level "P.O.S" を開けてみて
aespa's Next Level Open "P.O.S"
이건 real world 깨어났어
これは REAL WORLD 目覚めた
This is the REAL WORLD, I'm awake
We against the villain
What’s the name?
Black Mamba
woo-wee-woo wee aespa!
결국 난 문을 열어
ついに私はドアを開ける
I open the door in the end
그 빛은 네겐 Fire
その光は君にはFire
That light is like Fire to you
woo-wee-woo wee aespa!
난 궁금해 미치겠어
私は気になって狂いそう
I'm dying to know
이다음에 펼칠 story
この後繰り広げられるStory
The next Story that will unfold
Huh!
I’m on the Next Level
저 너머의 문을 열어
あの向こうのドアを開ける
I open the door over there
>Next Level 널
Next Level　君を
Next Level, I'll
결국엔 내가 부셔
ついには私が壊す
Destroy you in the end
Next Level KOSMO에 닿을 때까지
Next Level KOSMOに届くまで
Until I reach the Next Level KOSMO
>Next Level 제껴라 제껴라 제껴라
Next Level 追い抜け　追い抜け　追い抜け
Next Level, beat it, beat it, beat it
I’m on the Next Level
더 강해져 자유롭게
さらに強くなる　自由に
I become stronger and free
Next Level 난
Next Level　私は
Next Level, I'm
광야의 내가 아냐
KWANGYAの私じゃない
No longer who I was at KWANGYA
Next Level 야수 같은 나를 느껴
Next Level　野獣のような私を感じる
Next Level, Feel me I'm like a beast
Next Level 제껴라 제껴라 제껴라
Next Level　追い抜け　追い抜け　追い抜け
Next Level, beat it, beat it, beat it
Huh!